Friends, through this video we are going to
talk about the details of the quarterly results of ICICI Lord stock. The company has not updated anything
about dividend split or bonus around this level.
Only the plain and simple
December quarter results have been
published around this level. So let's
know about its results. See, the
figures which the company has mentioned for the results around this level have been
mentioned by the company according to these luxes, but I am going to
share it with you guys by calling it a card.
First let's know about the income of the December quarter.
So look at the net net, the total
income that we are getting to see is
around 588 283 crores. Its previous
quarter income was 585 065 and the
previous year's
income was 5424. So look, around this level,
we are getting to see a slight increase as per the previous quarter
and as per the previous year, we will
see around 3 to 4.
We are getting to see this increase, let us now
know about the expenses, see the
expenses are
around 519 747 crores and
in the previous quarter it
was around 5648 crores, its previous year
was around 4588 25 crores, so see its
expenses are much higher than the income, that is why the
company is getting to see the net net loss around this level, so in
this
quarter there is a loss of around 15000 230, in the
previous
quarter there was a
loss of around 1691 crores and in the
previous year there was a
loss of around 2844 crores, so
see this is plain and
simple, we are subtracting the expenses from the income,
let us now know about the net profit and loss,
what is the result after deducting the remaining taxes etc.,
so see profit and loss,
after these taxes etc. if you see, the
profit is around 72 crores 7243  It has happened that
in the previous quarter there was a profit of 69.3.95 and in the
previous year there
was a profit of 43.16, so see, as per the previous
quarter, we are going to see an increase in this profit around this level, as per the
previous year, a very
good income is being generated around this level,
so we should get to see a jump in the stock value,
friends,
please do support the channel by subscribing, let us
now know about its EPS value,
see, the EPS value which
we were getting to see around 14.05,
it has now increased to around 14.6.3 level,
how much quantity do you hold in this stock,
please do tell in the comment section